https://www.brunico.com/privacy/

Privacy
Privacy Policy of Brunico Communications Ltd. and its subsidiary Brunico Marketing Inc. (collectively referred to as "Brunico")
Protecting personal information and respecting personal privacy are very important to Brunico. This policy applies to all of Brunico's information practices and to all of its business operations, products, and services, including:
the print and electronic publications published by Brunico Communications Ltd., including Playback, Strategy, Media In Canada, Stimulant, Kidscreen, iKids, Realscreen, and STREAM ("Our Publications");
conferences and other events produced by Brunico Communications Ltd, and by its wholly-owned subsidiary, Brunico Marketing Inc. (collectively "Our Events");
websites related to Our Publications and Our Events ("Our Websites"); and
email newsletters related to Our Publications ("Our Email Newsletters").
Our Websites and Our Email Newsletters may contain links to third-party websites, for whose information practices Brunico is not responsible. When leaving Our Websites or Our Email Newsletters, please read the privacy policy applicable to the website to which any link is being made.
Personal Information
Personal information will not be collected and stored by Brunico, electronically or otherwise, without the knowledge and consent of the individual to whom it relates.
The purpose of collecting personal information is to be expressly stated by Brunico whenever solicited, and is not to be used for purposes other than those stated.
Personal information obtained by Brunico is not to be shared with third parties, unless the consent of the person to whom the personal information applies is obtained beforehand.
Information which Brunico treats as personal includes the following:
Credit card information;
Passwords;
Responses to validation questions asked for circulation audit purposes, such as year of birth or parent's first name;
Home address and contact information, unless identified to Brunico as being business address and contact information;
Mobile telephone numbers; and
Responses to opinion surveys, except to the extent that these are stated to be "for the record" and for publication.
Information which Brunico does not treat as personal for the purposes of this policy includes the following:
Individual's name;
Business title of the individual;
Individual's business function (e.g. sales, marketing, creative, engineering);
Name of the organization with which the individual is affiliated at the time that the information is obtained;
Industry sector and sub-sector describing the organization's activity;
Business mailing address;
Business telephone numbers;
Email address;
Website address of the organization or individual; and
Photos or videos of the individual.
To access or change your personal information, or for any matters pertaining to privacy of personal information, please contact Brunico:
Brunico Communications Ltd.Suite 100, 366 Adelaide St. WestToronto, Ontario, M5V 1R9, CanadaTelephone: 1-866-408-2300 or 416-408-0136Email: privacy@brunico.com
Personal information collected from Our Websites is always collected on a secure web server using 128-bit encryption.
Personal information is safeguarded on Brunico's servers. Access to the personal information on Brunico's servers is protected by the use of a security system, a firewall, passwords, and in some cases encryption.
Identifying Subscribers
An individual may be required to register on Our Websites to gain access to content. A registrant is normally required to supply non-personal information when creating his or her account, with the exception of a password. After registration, a small file (commonly called a "cookie") is created and stored on the registrantï¿½s computer to (a) maintain access to content and (b) facilitate the use of the Website through bypass of the sign-in process upon successive visits. The use of cookies is an industry standard and many websites use them.
Opting out
A recipient may, at any time, opt out of receiving any of Our Email Newsletters or emails from Brunico which inform about new products, services or information related to the industry by so indicating at the time that information is being given to Brunico, or thereafter, by following the simple steps stated in any such Brunico email received.
An individual may also deny permission or opt out of any previous permission given for Brunico to share address information with carefully screened third-party organizations by so indicating at the time that information is being given to Brunico, or by contacting Brunico's privacy officer (at the address shown above).
Accuracy of collected personal information
Brunico will from time to time on its own initiative, or immediately upon an individual's request, rectify or erase any incomplete, inaccurate or outdated personal information retained by Brunico.
Information that is no longer being used for the reasons stated upon collection is deleted from our databases after five years.
Non-personal information collected automatically
Non-personal information is collected from Our Websites in the form of web logs. The web logs are used to analyze anonymous behavior on Our Websites for the purposes of improving Brunico's products and services. On occasion aggregate statistics will be provided to reputable third-party companies, but these statistics will contain no personally identifiable information.
If you do not agree with this privacy policy, please do not use or subscribe to Our Websites, Our Publications or Our Email Newsletters.
Special Information For EU Users
SUMMARY
Beginning May 25, 2018, the processing of users’ personal data in the European Union is subject to the EU General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”).
This section summarizes Brunico’s grounds for processing personal information under the GDPR, and the rights of EU users as they relate to Brunico’s handling of personal information.
1. EU User Rights
If you are an Brunico user in the EU, you have the following rights with respect to Brunico's handling of your personal information:
a) Explanation and Copies of Your Data
You have the right to request an explanation of the information that Brunico has about you and how Brunico uses that information.
You also have the right to receive a copy of the information that Brunico collects about you if collected on the basis of consent, or because Brunico requires the information to provide the services that you request.
b) Correction
If Brunico has information about you that you believe is inaccurate, you have the right to request the correction of your information. Please see the section titled “Explanation, Copies and Correction” above for more information on correcting, or requesting correction of, your information.
c) Objections and Complaints
Users in the EU have the right to object to Brunico's processing of their personal data, including for marketing purposes. Brunico may continue to process your information, notwithstanding the objection to the extent permitted under GDPR.
Users in the EU also have the right to file a complaint relating to Brunico's handling of their personal information with the Autoriteit Persoonsgegevens, the Dutch Data Protection Authority. Its contact information is as follows:
Autoriteit PersoonsgegevensPostbus 933742509 AJ DEN HAAG+31-070-888-8500
You may also submit questions, comments or complaints to Brunico's Data Protection Officer by emailing <privacy@brunico.com>.
To exercise these rights, please submit your request by emailing <privacy@brunico.com>. Users outside the EU may also request explanation, correction, deletion or copies of their personal data here.
2. Grounds for Processing
The GDPR requires that companies processing the personal data of EU users do so on the basis of specific legal grounds. As described below, Brunico processes the information of EU users based on one or more of the grounds specified under the GDPR:
a) The processing is necessary to provide the services and features you request.
Brunico must collect and use certain information in order to provide its services. This includes:
i) User profile information that is necessary to establish and maintain your account, including to verify your identity; to enable communications with you about your event registration or subscription, orders and accounts; and/or to enable you to make payments.
ii) Transaction information that is necessary to generate and maintain in connection with your use of Brunico's services.
b) The processing is necessary to protect the vital interests of our users or of others.
Brunico may process personal information, including disclosing data with law enforcement authorities in case of threats to the safety of users or of others.
c) The processing is necessary for Brunico's legitimate interests.
Brunico collects and uses personal information to the extent necessary for its legitimate interests. This includes collecting and using information:
i) to provide customer support;
ii) to optimize our service and develop new services;
iii) for direct marketing purposes. (This includes, for example, analyzing data to identify trends and tailor marketing messages to user needs.)
iv) To enforce Brunico's Terms of Service.
d. The processing is necessary to fulfill Brunico's legal obligations.
Brunico is subject to legal requirements in the jurisdictions in which it operates that require us to collect, process, disclose and retain your personal data.
e. Consent
Brunico may collect and use your information on the basis of your consent. You may revoke your consent at any time. If you revoke your consent, you will not be able to use any service or feature that requires collection or use of the information we collected or used on the basis of consent.
Brunico relies on consent in connection with data collections or uses that are necessary to enhance the user experience, to enable optional services or features, or to communicate with you. If you are an EU user, the following types of data collections or uses are done on the basis of your consent.
Marketing emails
Newsletter emails
Print sales emails
Delegate news emails for events
Brunico may also collect personal information about you through voluntary surveys. Your responses to such surveys are collected on the basis of consent, and will be deleted once no longer necessary for the purposes collected.
This policy was last modified on July 27, 2018.
™ Brunico Communications Ltd. Site copyright © 1986-2020
title, tagline and logo of Brunico and all of its brands are trademarks of, and the events are produced by Brunico Marketing Inc.
